HADLEY **IGOE**

102 Ave Du Portage, Dartmouth, NS · 1(204)740-0152 Igoe.hadley@hotmail.ca W0199990@nscc.ca

OBJECTIVE

Work term for Spring 2019 and possible full-time employment.

SUMMARY

Currently enrolled in the Nova Scotia Community College IT Programming diploma – second year.

Seeking a work term for Spring 2019 and possible full-time employment.

I have the equivalent of 9 years of full time work experience in medical, retail, and food service.

EXPERIENCE

Server (Part-Time 20-30HRS/Week) Swiss Chalet, Dartmouth, NS 06/2018 – 09/2018

I work with a team of servers, kitchen staff and management to provide great customer service and an amazing dining experience for all guests.

Computer Tech (Part-Time 8HRS/Week)

Terrane Geoscience, Halifax, NS 05/2018 - 09/2018

I worked with a small team of Geologists to manage all their data on the server, created manuals and performed other light duties as required for the first-year work term. When my work-term was completed, they offered me part time employment for the remainder of the summer.

Medical Lab Technician (Part-Time 32HRS/Week)

Family Practice associates, Halifax, NS 03/2017 - 09/2018

I work with a team of 4 people to provide excellent customer service and communicate a positive attitude to our long-term patients. Doing our best to keep them comfortable and relaxed while providing a multitude of different medical procedures.

Medical Lab Technician (Part-Time 15-20HRS/Week)

Capital Health, Halifax, NS 12/2016 - 03/2017

Preforming phlebotomy in a team setting in which I collected an average of 30 patient samples in a 3-hour span while keeping the patients safety as a top priority

Logistics Coordinator

Vandaele Seeds Medora, MB 04/2016 – 09/2016

Worked alongside my supervisor to problem solve, track, schedule and organize seed and grain trucks across Canada and America. We were responsible to keep records and schedules for trucks, customers, and the bagging area.

Medical Lab Assistant - Microbiology

Westman Laboratory, Brandon, MB 09/2012 - 04/2016

Worked in a team setting of 4-6 where we processed approximately 100 samples per day to data enter and process. Our team would have an error rate of about 0.2% per week. Required to keep up with current practices through annual competencies

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE - FRONT END DEVELOPMENT

Light House Labs, Halifax, NS July 2018 – August 2018

DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY PROGRAMMING

Nova Scotia Community College, Halifax, NS 2017-2019

DIPLOMA IN MEDICAL LABORATORY TECHNICIAN

Robertson College, Brandon, MB May 25, 2011 Graduated with honors

IT SKILLS

- Intro to Windows Administration
- Local Area Network Concepts
- Intro to Database Management Systems using Access
- MS SQL Server
- Introduction to Programming using Python
- Introduction to Web Development using HTML 5, CSS 3, PHP and JavaScript
- Technical Communications and Intro to Project Management
- Object Oriented Programming using Java/C#
- Transactional Database Programming
- Intro to Unix Operating Systems
- System Analysis and Design
- Programming in C, C++, & C#
- User interface Design and Development
- Android Development

REFERENCES

Can be provided on request.